[
  {
    "question": "Urdu was declared national language of Pakistan in:",
    "choice1": "April 1950",
    "choice2": "April 1955",
    "choice3": "April 1954",
    "choice4": "April 1952",
    "answer": 3
    
  },
  {
    "question": " In which province maximum languages are spoken?",
    "choice1": "Sindh",
    "choice2": "Punjab",
    "choice3": "Balochistan",
    "choice4": "Khyber PK",
    "answer": 1
  
  },
  {
    "question": " Which Urdu has been taken from the following language:",
    "choice2": "Turkish",
    "choice3": "Arabic",
    "choice4": "Persian",
    "choice1": " None of these",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Durand line was demarcated in 1893. This line forms:",
    "choice1": "Pak-China border",
    "choice2": "Pak-Afghan border",
    "choice3": "Pak-India border",
    "choice4": "Pak-Iran border",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which peak is located in Karakorum Range ?",
    "choice1": "K-2",
    "choice2": "Nanga Patbat",
    "choice3": "Rakaposhi",
    "choice4": "Takht-e-Sulaiman",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Urdu was declared national language of Pakistan in:",
    "choice1": "April 1950",
    "choice2": "April 1955",
    "choice3": "April 1954",
    "choice4": "April 1952",
    "answer": 3
    
  },
  {
    "question": " In which province maximum languages are spoken?",
    "choice1": "Sindh",
    "choice2": "Punjab",
    "choice3": "Balochistan",
    "choice4": "Khyber PK",
    "answer": 1
  
  },
  {
    "question": " Which Urdu has been taken from the following language:",
    "choice2": "Turkish",
    "choice3": "Arabic",
    "choice4": "Persian",
    "choice1": " None of these",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Durand line was demarcated in 1893. This line forms:",
    "choice1": "Pak-China border",
    "choice2": "Pak-Afghan border",
    "choice3": "Pak-India border",
    "choice4": "Pak-Iran border",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which peak is located in Karakorum Range ?",
    "choice1": "K-2",
    "choice2": "Nanga Patbat",
    "choice3": "Rakaposhi",
    "choice4": "Takht-e-Sulaiman",
    "answer": 1
  }
  
]
